A Guide to the Memorabilia FA437
Rockefeller Archive Center
- John D. Rockefeller, Jr., 3
  - portrait of hands of Martha Baird Rockefeller, 1927; 16 x 22.25; see #2032 (Object 2033)
  - portrait made of lines from "I Believe" creed, 1975; 21.25 x 18.25 (Object 2034, Box 9)
  - 2 illuminated scrolls in gold coffer from Univ. of Paris, 1936 November 14; in blue case w/ initials (Object 2035)
  - violin in case, very bad condition (Object 2036)
  - collapsible music stand (Object 2037, Box 3)
  - red leather suitcase "M.B.R.", 11 x 15 (Object 2038, Box 1)
  - hardshell suitcase "M.B.R.", 11 x 15 (Object 2039, Box 1)
  - correspondence w/ Adm. Byrd w/ 2 flags from North & South Pole Expeditions, & small crucifix, 1926, 1929, 1935; correspondence separated to flat files (same #), crucifix in small box, flags in envelope (Object 2040, Box 2)
  - inscribed silver Conservation Award, Massachusetts Trustees of Public Reservations, 1939 January (Object 2041, Box 9)
  - Allied Arts Prize, Architectural League of NY, 1956 December (Object 2042, Box 2)
  - mini table w/ pamphlet "Colorado Industrial Plan", 1915; w/ note (Object 2043, Box 2)
  - Lincoln statue, award from United Negro College Fund, 1958 April 14; w/ note separated to flat files (same #) (Object 2044, Box 2)
  - Honorary chairman plaque, USO, 1956 November 13 (Object 2045, Box 9)
  - gavel made from wood from home of C.H. Apthorp, w/letter from J. Goldy of East Ohio Gas Co, Cleveland 7/8/38, 1874 January 29 (Object 2046, Box 2)
  - plaque & correspondence, American School of Studies in Athens/Overland Corporation, w/ replicas of Greek voting disks, w/ correspondence, 1957 May 24; correspondence separated to flat files (same #) (Object 2047, Box 9)
  - Humble Oil desk set w/ 2 medallions in base and 2 ink pens in tube w/note, Houston TX, 1944 December 14; commemorates 1 billion gallons of octane gas (Object 2048, Box 2)
  - bronze seal of American School in Athens, 1959 March 31; correspondence removed to flat files (Object 2049, Box 9)
  - Grand Cross of the Royal Order of the Phoenix, Greece, 1957 May 11; correspondence removed to flat files, 2 medals (Object 2050, Box 9)
  - Grand Cross of Royal Order of Greece to JR-2 medals, 1937 October 15 (Object 2051, Box 3)
  - commemorative coin from Versailles, 1956 June 26 (Object 2052, Box 5)
  - portrait of JR by Comtesse Greffulhe as wedding gift, 1936; sent to Martha Baird Rockefeller (Object 2053, Box 9)
  - copy of letter from Jr to Monica Moore (RF), 1920 May 20 (Object 2054, Box 9)
  - silver tray w/ signatures of Harbor Club Board in place of "favorable lease", w/ note, 1947; in red case (Object 2055)
  - shoulder-knot cape w/medal, Honorary Doctorate from, 1930; in blue triangular box (Object 2056, Box 4)
  - U. of Brussels Medical School (Object 2056, Box 4)
  - resolution from GEB upon his retirement, 1939 April 6; bound album in matching case (Object 2057, Box 8)
  - book of letters from Williamsburg residents, w/ letter, 1929 December (Object 2058, Box 8)
  - citation from Riverside Church, 1959 December 6; bound album in envelope (Object 2059, Box 8)
  - citation, menu, etc from wartime service reception, 1947 October 24 (Object 2060, Box 8)
  - stamps commemorating flights of Italian Gen. Balboa, 1933; bound album in envelope (Object 2061, Box 9)
  - gold engraved plate, opening of the Cloisters Museum, 1938 May 10 (Object 2062, Box 3)
  - Legion of Honor writ for Abby, 1933 April 15; in tube (Object 2063)
  - 2 medals from America's Cup Races, for Winthrop Aldrich's boat "Shamrock V", won 4 races, 1930 (Object 2064, Box 5)
  - bronze bear statue, Brown Univ. Alumni class of 1897, 1956 June 1 (Object 2065, Box 3)
  - bound writ of thanks for Rigot property, U. of Geneva, 1942; in large red album (Object 2066, Box 10)
  - map of Adm. Byrd expeditions in Antarctica, w/ notes, 1959 February 13; correspondence stored separately (Object 2067)
  - box of canceled checks from Banker's Trust Co., 1915 April-1916; check #s N. H-11927 to H-13900 (Object 2068, Box 2)
  - mini Greek statue from Parthenon, w/ note, 1956 September 3 (Object 2069)
    from Amer. School of Classic Studies at Athens
  - key & plaque from coffer given by France, 1927 December 17 (Object 2070, Box 2)
  - Legion of Honor Grand Croix, 1936; 2 medals (Object 2071, Box 5)
  - Greek Cross of High Commander, 1935; 2 medals (Object 2072, Box 5)
  - Monuments Historiques de France (Object 2073, Box 5)
  - Societe des Architectes medal, 1924 (Object 2074, Box 5)
  - bronze medal, unlabeled, 1919 (Object 2075, Box 5)
  - Order of the Crown, Belgium-Commander, 1920 (Object 2076, Box 5)
  - Order of the Crown, Belgium-Grand Officer, 1930; correspondence (Object 2077, Box 9)
  - Order of the Crown, Belgium-Grand Officer (Object 2077, Box 5)
  - Les Musees Nationaux medal, 1929 (Object 2078, Box 5)
  - gold coin from University of Paris (Object 2079, Box 5)
  - engraved Chinese coin w/note (Object 2080, Box 5)
  - John H. Finley Award, NYC-gold coin, 1948 December 2; see old #s 10, 13 (Object 2081, Box 5)
  - 7 Legion of Honor Grand Officer buttons, 1933; in 2 matching boxes (Object 2082, Box 5)
  - medal from Council of Museums, France, w/letter, 1929 December 23 (Object 2083, Box 5)
  - World Student Christian Fed. medal from Peking, China, 1922 April (Object 2084, Box 5)
    from 11th annual conference
  - billfold w/honorary membership card from Local 795 from O.P. and F.I.A., w/ letter from NAR, 1950 (Object 2085, Box 3)
  - Marcellus Hartley Award, Natll Academy of Sciences, 1943 April 26; bound album in white box (Object 2086, Box 8)
  - Special Grand Jury gavel, 1910 June; in wooden box (Object 2087, Box 5)
  - medal from Welfare Council of NYC, 1947 May 14 (Object 2088, Box 5)
  - Rosenberg Medal from Brown University, w/ speech, 1931; speech separated to flat files (Object 2089, Box 9)
  - Medal from Architectural Societies of NY w/ clipping, 1942 (Object 2090, Box 5)
  - 2 Elisie Willing Balch medals, Colonial Dames of PA, 1929 (Object 2091, Box 5)
  - Michael Friedsam Medal, w/ clipping, 1939 (Object 2092, Box 5)
  - Garden Club of Virginia Medal, 1935 (Object 2093, Box 5)
  - AIA Apartment House medal for Dunbar Apartment design, 1928 (Object 2094, Box 5)
  - AIA Apartment House medal for Thomas Garden Apts, 1929 (Object 2095, Box 5)
  - Natll Council of State Garden Clubs medal, 1950 April (Object 2096, Box 5)
    Scope and Contents
    given in Williamsburg
  - St. Nicholas Society of NY medal, 1947 October 4 (Object 2097, Box 5)
  - Natll Academy of Sciences bronze medal, 1943 (Object 2099, Box 5)
  - medal from The Virginians, 1935; speech separated to flat files (Object 2100, Box 5)
  - medal from The Virginians - speech, 1935 (Object 2100, Box 9)
  - 100 Year Club of New York medal, 1935 (Object 2101, Box 5)
  - bronze coin from Adm. Byrd North Pole expedition, 1926 (Object 2102, Box 5)
  - Natll Institute of Social Sciences medal, 1919; missing (Object 2103)
  - Natll Institute of Social Sciences medal, 1929; documents separated to flat files (Object 2104, Box 5)
  - Natll Institute of Social Sciences medal - notes, 1929; Documents. (Object 2104, Box 9)
  - Grand Street Boys medal, 1941 (Object 2105, Box 5)
  - Edison Golden Jubilee bronze miniature plaque, 1929 (Object 2106, Box 5)
  - 2 Chamber of Commerce medals, 1919 (Object 2107, Box 5)
  - Girl Scouts badge-given on their 21st annversary, 1933 (Object 2108, Box 5)
  - Alpha Delta Phi and lobster pins (Object 2109, Box 5)
  - Honorary member button, from VA Sons of Revolution, 1934 February 22 (Object 2110, Box 5)
  - member pin of Cammerian Club, Brown University, 1882 (Object 2111, Box 5)
  - nautical pin from yacht cruise "H.A.P.A.G.", 1896 July (Object 2112, Box 5)
  - Honorary member badge, Hilltop Fire Company P.H., 1941 (Object 2113, Box 5)
  - Phi Beta Kappa key, with notes (Object 2114, Box 5)
  - buttons of the Order of Cincinnati, w/ notes, 1936 January 28 (Object 2115, Box 5)
  - buttons of the Order of Cincinnati, w/ notes, 1929 (Object 2116, Box 5)
  - 4 booklets on the Order of the Cincinnati, Georgia, tied together (Object 2117, Box 9)
  - life membership in Oregon Trail Memorial Assoc. (Object 2118)
  - tribute from International House Family (Chicago), 1957 September 8 (Object 2119, Box 4)
    25th anniversary of founding
  - tribute from International House Family (Object 2120)
    35th anniversary of founding
  - bound letters signed by Russian refugees in thanks, 1921-1923 (Object 2121)
  - citation to JR from VA for Williamsburg restorations, oversized red album in matching box (Object 2122, Box 4)
  - album of scores JDR played on violin (Object 2123, Box 10)
    JR's music 1883-1890 (ags 9-16)
  - commendation, President's War Relief Control Board, 1946 May 15 (Object 2124, Box 9)
  - Scroll of Honor, Citizens of New York, 1935 (Object 2125)
  - Patron of the New York Historical Society, 1925 November 10 (Object 2126)
  - U.S. Dept of State recognizing MRS. JR for donations to Brussels University Intll Exhibition, 1958 October (Object 2127)
  - crystal globe, in tribute from UN Ambassador Dinner, 1986 September 17; heavy & fragile (Object 2128, Box 3)
  - 2 copies of resolution from YMCA, 1960 May 25; rolled (Object 2129, Box 6)
  - member, World League for Peace, 1930 November 14 (Object 2130, Box 6)
  - honorary doctorate from RU on scroll, signed by David R., 1959 May 22 (Object 2131, Box 7)
  - embroidered linen umbrella holder (?) w/ empty black case inside, made by JDR JR (Object 2132)
  - collage of Roanoke College, VA, w/photo of JR. & Rev. Goodwin, 1975 October 16; 17 x 27 (Object 2133)
  - cartoon in Colorado, from Denver Post, 1915 October (Object 2134)
  - plaque from Chamber of Commerce of Tarrytown, Irvington, N. Tarrytown for 45 years of residence, 1938 April 4 (Object 2135)
  - page from The Evening World: Daily Magazine w/ message from JR campaigning for returning troops, 1918 November 11 (Object 2136)
  - 2 pages from Reporter Dispatch on Ruth Taylor & other Westchester founding figures, 1961 June 23 (Object 2137, Box 9)
    Copies are available for scholarly access.
  - 1980 Westchester Community Profile poster, 2 framed proclamations, case (Object 2138)
  - portrait in oil paint (Object 2139)
  - 2 strong boxes, used to hold medals (Object 2140)
- John D. Rockefeller 3rd, 4
  - Margaret Sanger Award (Object 3000, Box 7)
  - Plaque from Operation Brotherhood in Vietnam, 1957 October 14; in red box (Object 3001, Box 7)
  - Young Men's Christian Association Honor, 1960 November 17 (Object 3002, Box 7)
  - Commemorative Album of Japanese Royalty's Visit to the United States, 1960 (Object 3003, Box 6)
  - Order of Rising Sun Proclamation, Emperor of Japan, 1968; in small wood box (Object 3004)
  - Large Painted Japanese Scroll "From Mr. Kagaya", in medium wood box (Object 3005)
  - Silver Vase with Teakwood Stand, from Emperor of Japan, 1975 October 1; in large wood box: FRAGILE (Object 3006)
  - Gold Award, Albert Lasker Award, Planned Parenthood, 1961 October 24; citation stored separately (Object 3008, Box 2)
  - Gold Award - Citation, Albert Lasker Award, Planned Parenthood, 1961 October 24 (Object 3008, Box 6)
  - box of medals, w/ 3 dogtags, 3 ribbons, 5 pins, 1 ID bracelet (Object 3009, Box 2)
  - medal, Commander of Order of Arts and Letters, France, 1958 October 1; w/ letter (Object 3010, Box 2)
  - Copies of the Key to Seoul, South Korea, with note (2), 1965 February 19 (Object 3011, Box 1)
  - quote, presented by associates for his 70th birthday, 1976 March 21; bound in green book & box (Object 3012, Box 8)
  - notes & decree of Honorary Commander of British Empire, 1947 April 18 (Object 3013, Box 8)
  - Silver Plate from 20th Anniversary of International House of Japan, 1972 November 14; signed, in green box (Object 3014)
  - Signed Photo of Prince & Princess Hitachi of Japan, in velvet box (Object 3015, Box 4)
  - signed photo of Emperor & Empress of Japan, 1975 October 1; in velvet box (Object 3016, Box 4)
  - honorary doctorate, Manhattan College, 1959 June 1; in green tube (Object 3017, Box 5)
  - Public Service Award, Princeton University, 1967 April 1; see #3089 (Object 3018, Box 5)
  - Poster of Westway State Park, New York Parks and Recreation, 1984 (Object 3019, Box 5)
  - Writ from Commission on Population Growth and the American Future, signed with photos, 1972 March 9; bound in brown album (Object 3020, Box 6)
  - Declaration, Seoul National University, South Korea, to Population Council, 1965 February 20; mounted in velvet book (Object 3021, Box 11)
  - decree, Knight Grand Cross of Order of Crown, Thailand, 1960 July 5; 3 documents in envelope (Object 3022, Box 11)
  - Academic Hood, Yonsei University, South Korea, in teak box, 1965 February 20 (Object 3023, Box 3)
  - metal case, from PM Kittikachorn of Thailand, 1975 January 26 (Object 3024, Box 2)
  - Tiffany silver/wood box from Calvin Bullock Forum (Object 3025, Box 2)
  - medals in wood hinged box, Public Service Award, 1967 April 12 (Object 3026, Box 2)
  - trowel, cornerstone laying of Ramon Magsaysay Center, 1967 September 2 (Object 3027, Box 2)
    from Manila, Phillipines
  - Nameplate, Corporation for Public Broadcasting Directors, 1968-1970 (Object 3028, Box 2)
  - decree of honorary doctorate, Yonsei University, 1965 February 20 (Object 3029, Box 6)
  - award, American Public Health Association, 1974; silver cube in red box (Object 3030, Box 1)
  - decree of Order of Sikatuna, rank of Datu, from Philippines, 1967 September 1; in box w/ medal (Object 3031, Box 10)
  - medals, Order of Sikatuna, rank of Datu, from Philippines, 1967 September 1; 2 medals and sash in box (Object 3032, Box 10)
  - Portrait of King of Afghanistan, 1963 December 9; in tan box (Object 3033)
  - Medallion, inauguration of President Marcos of Philippines, 1965 December 30 (Object 3034, Box 2)
  - Honorary Doctorate, Hebrew Union College-Jewish Institute, 1961 June 18 (Object 3035, Box 5)
  - Award, West Side Association of Commerce, New York City, 1958 November 18 (Object 3036, Box 1)
  - President's Award, Society for Personal Administration, 1958 June 3 (Object 3037, Box 5)
  - large decree of Grand White Cordon w/ Red Borders, Order of the Jade, Republic of China, 1936 February 10; Oversized (Object 3038)
  - 2 folders of clippings from 1st Magsaysay Foundation Awards in Manila w/ JDR III & daughter Sandra, 1957 (Object 3040, Box 9)
  - decree, speech, & program, Woodrow Wilson Award, Princeton University Alumni, 1973 February 24 (Object 3041, Box 9)
  - signed portrait of President of India, 1963 June 1 (Object 3042)
  - resolution, Colonial Williamsburg Foundation, 1978 September 13; bound in brown album (Object 3043, Box 11)
  - album from Lord & Taylor Award Luncheon: photos, clippings, A/V, etc, 1955 May 16; bound in green album (Object 3044, Box 11)
  - Honorary membership paperweight, Governor's Club (Object 3045, Box 2)
  - Richard Nixon campaign paperweight, 1968 (Object 3046, Box 2)
  - inlaid plaque from City of Seoul, Korea, 1965? (Object 3047, Box 3)
  - "The Bicentennial Tapestries" book of Calder's tapestries (Object 3048, Box 6)
    w/ note in red folder
  - promo materials from opening night of Lincoln Center w/ photos, slides, film reels and pamphlet, 1962 September 23; documents/photos separated (Object 3049, Box 9)
  - promo materials from opening night of Lincoln Center w/ photos, slides, film reels and pamphlet, documents/photos. (Object 3049)
  - LBJ's nomination to Public Broadcasting Corporation, 1968 March 13 (Object 3050, Box 9)
    w/ note from LBJ
  - envelope of "fragments from JRD 3rd's room chair", scraps of wood in an envelope (Object 3051)
  - small key marked "#179" (Object 3052)
  - mounted photo of Lincoln Center opening night, from Life, 1962 September 23 (Object 3053)
  - LBJ commendation, Public Service Awards Dinner, 1967 April 12 (Object 3054)
  - Honorary citizen of Versailles decree, w/ painting, 1954 February 17; bound in oversized leather album (Object 3055)
  - decorative sewing box, possibly Asian (Object 3056, Box 2)
  - Chinese certificate, Order of the Auspicious Star, info from note on envelope (Object 3057, Box 9)
  - academic hood-Princeton? (Object 3058, Box 2)
  - ornate framed photo of King & Queen of Thailand, signed, 1960 (Object 3059, Box 11)
  - photos from Rock. Public Service Awards Dinner, flat files (Object 3060)
  - "Views from Gov's Island" poster, Delbart Duchein, w/note, 1976; note & poster in tube (Object 3061)
  - academic procession robes & degree hood (Object 3062, Box 7)
  - framed photos of Prince & Princess of Japan, in matching wood boxes w/ ties (Object 3063, Box 4)
  - letter from Gov. of Tokyo on Japan Society Exhibit, 1977 April 10; in blue book (Object 3064, Box 6)
  - Grand Cordon Star of Ethiopia, from Emperor, 1954 June 2; in red velvet box w/ photo (Object 3065, Box 3)
  - signed photo of Emperor Haile Selassie I of Ethiopia, 1954 June 2; in red velvet box w/ medal (Object 3066)
  - Greater NY Fund Campaign Resolution, 1905 May 2 (Object 3067)
  - Concert Artists Guild Award, for Lincoln Center, 1964 April 8 (Object 3068)
  - Gold Baton Award, from Amer. Symphony Orchestra League, 1963 June 22 (Object 3069)
  - "A Salute to America" by John Buchanan, Bicentenary ed., 1976 (Object 3070, Box 6)
  - citation from recipients of Rock. Public Service Awards, 1972 December 6 (Object 3071)
  - Scroll of Merit, from NY Board of Trade, 1965 June 3 (Object 3072)
  - Citation on Ceparture from Corporation for Public Broadcasting, 1970 September 18 (Object 3073)
  - Gold Medal Award, National Institute of Social Sciences, 1967 November 28 (Object 3074)
  - Gold Medal Award, National Institute of Social Sciences (Object 3074)
  - resolution of appreciation, International House in NY, 1977 April 13 (Object 3075, Box 9)
  - Distinguished Service Award, from Loomis-Chaffee School, 1975 June 7 (Object 3076, Box 9)
  - Service Award, from American Medical Association, 1969 July 15 (Object 3077)
  - U.S. Dept of Interior dedication as natll historic landmark (Object 3078)
    doesn't specify which house
  - plaque from Federation of Jewish Philanthropies of NY, 1964 October 4 (Object 3079)
  - citation, Men's Club of Stephen Wise Free Synagogue, 1960 October 16 (Object 3080)
  - signed Organ Encores by Dick Leibert at Radio City (Object 3081)
  - Broadway Association Gold Medal certificate and medal, 1962 November 13; packed separately (Object 3082, Box 1)
  - Fine Arts Museums of San Franciscon resolution, 1978 January 19 (Object 3083)
  - Grand Cordon, Order of Sacred Treasure, 1st class, from Emperor Hirohito of Japan, 1954 February 25 (Object 3084, Box 9)
  - Collection of newspaper clippings, obituaries, etc, 1978 July 1; flat files (Object 3085)
  - plaque in thanks, Ramon Magsaysay Award Foundation, 1958 (Object 3086, Box 7)
  - appt to Commission on Population Growth, from Nixon, 1970 March 16; see # 3088, rolled (Object 3087, Box 5)
  - small brass box w/ mushrooms on it, w/ note, from Commission on Population Growth?, see # 3087 (Object 3088, Box 1)
  - 2 Princeton lapel rosettes, as sign of Rock Public Service Award, see #3018 (Object 3089, Box 1)
  - Sesquicentennial Award,University of Michigan medal, 1967 November 16; citation stored separately (Object 3090, Box 2)
  - Sesquicentennial Award,University of Michigan, citation, 1967 November 16; Medal stored separately. (Object 3090, Box 9)
  - name plate, member of Charter Trustees, Princeton, 1967 June 12 (Object 3091, Box 1)
  - mini silver platter, from speaking at NY Chamber of Commerce, 1959 June 4 (Object 3092, Box 1)
  - plaque, Youth's Voices of Democracy, 1950 February 27 (Object 3093, Box 2)
  - 100 Year Association of NY Inc Gold Medal Award, 1959 October 6 (Object 3094, Box 1)
  - bronze medal, Citizens Budget Commission, 1961 January 11 (Object 3095, Box 1)
  - Special Award from Tony Awards for Lincoln Center development, 1960 April 24 (Object 3096, Box 1)
  - medal, key note address as President of Wesleyan College, 1973 September 28 (Object 3097, Box 1)
  - 2 papal medals from visits in UN, India, Rome, 1965 July, October (Object 3098, Box 1)
  - George Frideric Handel medal, from Mayor Wagner of NYC, 1964 April 8 (Object 3099, Box 1)
  - poem by Elizabeth F.Coonley from dedication at Vassar (Object 3100, Box 8)
  - resolution from Board of Directors, Lincoln Center, 1992 December 14 (Object 3101, Box 11)
  - honorary degree, from the Juilliard School, 1987 May 22 (Object 3102, Box 11)
  - documents and booklet "Statement on Population Stabilization by World Leaders," presented to UN, 1985 October 24 (Object 3103, Box 8)
  - album of commemorative stamps from Russia, 1988 (Object 3105, Box 8)
  - Private Sector Initiatve Commendation, from Pres. Reagan, 1985 (Object 3106)
  - National Legion of Honor, order of Knight, 1987 March 20 (Object 3107)
  - appt to NY State Council on the Arts, 1981 July 2 (Object 3108)
  - degree, Vassar College, 1931 (Object 3109)
  - NYC Mayor's Award for Arts and Culture, 1981 June 23 (Object 3110)
  - 20th anniversary citation from Channel 13, NYC, 1983 June 8 (Object 3111)
  - appt to National Council on the Humanities from Nixon, 1974 June 10 (Object 3112)
  - signed portrait of President Ford, 1970s (Object 3113)
  - Business' Speak Gold Award, NY Board of Trade Inc, 1957 October 10 (Object 3120, Box 1)
  - plaque, Joint Board of the Electrical Industry for Lincoln Center, 1962 January 6 (Object 3121, Box 1)
  - corn-shaped award, Des Moines Dinner Club, 1952 September 17 (Object 3122, Box 1)
  - The Parents Magazine Medal, mounted in wood, 1967 (Object 3123, Box 1)
  - plaque from The Arts Council, Winston-Salem NC, 1958 November 9 (Object 3124, Box 1)
  - collage from RF visit to Earl K. Long hospital visit in L.A., 1969 March 10 (Object 3125)
  - Society for the Family of Man Award-gold coin, 1968 October 23 (Object 3126, Box 2)
- Laurance S. Rockefeller, 5
  - award from Business Council for the UN, to DR & LSR, 1986 September 17; in white box "LSR" (Object 4000)
  - certificate at Arctic Circle, from Wien Alaska Airlines, 1963 July 6 (Object 4001)
  - dollar sign pin, "Toward the Conquest of Cancer" (Object 4002, Box 3)
  - silver coin for "annual gift", University of Texas, 1985 (Object 4003, Box 3)
  - paperweight w/ piece of Berlin Wall (Object 4004, Box 3)
  - bronze coin from Reader's Digest "Valitut Palat", 1985 (Object 4005, Box 3)
  - 40th anniversary edition Danish Reader's Digest, w/ note, 1985 (Object 4006, Box 6)
  - 2 cardcases, John E. Fetzer Foundation Dedication, 1988 June 25 (Object 4007, Box 3)
  - cardcase, Reader's Digest Valogatas, Budapest, 1991 (Object 4008, Box 3)
  - paperweight, Boys' Clubs of America President's Dinner, 1990 June 26 (Object 4009, Box 3)
  - 2 bronze coins, Boys Clubs of NY Sports Hall of Fame Dinner, 1985, 1987 (Object 4010, Box 3)
  - University of Vermont print, 1987 (Object 4011)
  - bronze plate w/ LBJ quote, given by director of LBJ library, 2000 March 9 (Object 4012, Box 6)
  - Salk Institute for Biological Studies citation, 1993 February 1 (Object 4013, Box 5)
  - New Media Bible: sound and film strips, 1976; in large black clamshell (Object 4014)
  - memorial for Horace M. Albright, from Jackson Hole Preserve Inc, w/ extra copies in folder, 1987 September 2; bound in blue clamshell book (Object 4015)
  - memorial for Nancy Hanks, Jackson Hole Preserve Inc, 1983 September 13; bound in blue clamshell (Object 4016, Box 6)
  - 11 blueprints & watercolors for residence in Tarrytown, 1965 (Object 4017)
  - "Our Corporate Values" writ from Reader's Digest, Oversized (Object 4018)
  - photo of Buddha mounted w/ Tibetan print, signed from Karma Triyana Dharmachakra monastary in NY (Object 4019)
  - signed plaque from RockResorts, 1986 April 1; Oversized (Object 4020)
  - remarks from Reader's Digest groundbreaking in Canada, 1961 October 31; Oversized (Object 4021)